In this video, I will introduce the relevant functions of the material for you.
In the previous version, we can only attach one point on the component.
In the 2025 version, we have improved the interaction between the component and the clothing.
Now we can attach multiple points of the same component to the clothing.
For complex component styles, we may need to attach two or more points of the component.
First, we can use the option to move the tool to select the component.
Then click the quick arrangement button.
Place the component near the ideal position of the clothing.
This is a simple placement process and will not produce any adhesion effect.
In the new version, the tool is combined with the component.
The operation is similar to fixing the plate to the plate.
The tool is combined with the component.
Using the tool, we can click the point on the component.
Then click the point to be attached to the clothing.
The first group of points is created.
We can use the same method to attach the second group of points on the component.
These points will be displayed in dark red and virtual.
Let's see the result after opening the simulation.
The two points on the component are perfectly integrated on the clothing.
If necessary, you can also attach more points on the component.
If you want to edit the position of the armor, please use the edit armor tool.
You can edit in 3D and 2D windows.
Just select the point of the armor and drag its position.
Open the simulation and check the effect.
To delete the armor, just select it.
Then right-click to delete on the menu.
Or press the delete button.
Therefore, you can now decide to attach one point or more points according to the component type.
To achieve a more realistic simulation effect.
In the 2025.0 version,
You can follow the designated naming method.
After adding the pattern to the text,
Automatically import other PBR stickers.
First, before importing PBR stickers,
We need to store all PBR stickers in the same folder.
Then change the name of the sticker according to the name of the file.
We need to follow the name of the image, the draft line, and the name of the PBR sticker.
These three components of the image naming rule.
To ensure that all PBR stickers can be correctly imported.
The image name should be placed at the beginning.
The name can be self-defined.
Each PBR sticker uses the same image name.
The software can identify that these stickers belong to the same group.
The draft line is behind the image name.
And in the middle of the entire name.
The PBR sticker name should be placed at the end.
The name of the PBR sticker also needs to follow the naming rule.
It will affect the import position of the picture in the clover attribute editor.
To do this,
You can use the content shown now.
Name your own PBR stickers.
You can also refer to the official website for detailed information.
In the attribute editor.
Let's import the text sticker.
Click the browse button.
Find the folder where the PBR stickers are placed.
Select the text.
Then click open.
At this time, you will see a pop-up message.
Ask whether to continue.
Click yes.
In the attribute editor,
Add the text sticker and other PBR stickers at the same time.
Click no.
Just add the text sticker.
Other PBR stickers in the attribute editor.
Will not be imported or updated.
Here we click yes.
You can see that the text sticker and other PBR stickers.
One is added to the corresponding position.
You can also import new text stickers.
To replace the existing text stickers in the attribute editor.
Other related PBR stickers will be added and updated at the same time.
You can also add other PBR stickers in addition to the fabric.
Use this new function.
For example, stickers.
Self-defined name line and so on.
With this new function.
You can upload all PBR stickers at once.
And paste the picture.
The following is the 2025 version.
About the improvement of the text editor.
There are two points in total.
One is that you can provide more picture format options.
Use the format that you need to save the picture.
The other is to support the storage of combined layer images.
Open the text editor.
We can add more pictures.
And edit these pictures.
To achieve various design effects.
After editing and adjusting the settings.
Click Save Picture to save the picture result.
Users can click below the window.
Select the picture format.
You can export the selected picture to the desired format.
Now support PNG, JPEG and TIFF three file formats.
Therefore, you can choose the file format according to your needs.
You can also choose whether to save the combined layer image.
After selecting the layer image to be saved and combined.
Add an additional layer image to the combined layer images.
At the same time, the separated text layer images will be stored normally.
If you cancel the selection.
Only separate single text layer images are stored in the existing rules.
This is the same as the default storage result before.
Here, click OK after setting up.
Open the storage folder.
You can see the single layer image and combined image stored.
By providing multiple image formats and new storage options.
When users use the text editor to design the text.
It has more flexibility.